freeweburlsubmit.com 2012-06-17

# Submit Free Web Url - Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

**General**  
Your privacy is important to us. FreeWebUrlSubmit.com commits us to protecting and respecting your privacy when visiting our website. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for our website. 

**Information We Collect**

We may collect the required data about you like information that you provide by filling the forms on our site. This includes provided information at the time of submitting your URL, requesting further services or subscribing to any service offered by us on the site. Details of the resources, you access or submitted and your visits to our site. We do not use this information for any other purpose and we do not provide or sell this information to any third parties 

**Use of Information Collected**

We use the information that is collected from you to notify you of any changes to our site and services. We also use your data to be contacted, to provide you with the information, products and services requested from us. 

**IP ADDRESSES AND COOKIES  
**   
We may collect information about your computer; this is statistical data concerning your browsing actions and does not identify you individually. This information includes your IP address where available, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report collective information to our advertisers. 

A cookie is a small file stored on your computer by a web site to give you a unique ID. We use Cookies and other technologies to track new visitors to this Site and recognize past customers so that we may present more personalized content. Cookies used by this Site do not contain any personally identifiable information. We cannot identify a customer unless that information is provided voluntarily. 

**Links**

This Site may contain links to other sites that are not owned, maintained, operated, or endorsed by or for freeweburlsubmit.com and not subject to the same Privacy and other Policies. We are not responsible for the content of those sites or the use of any information collected from you by those sites. The inclusion of any link to such sites does not imply any recommendation or sponsorship of such sites. 

**Advertisers**

We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.co.uk/privacy_ads.html).

**CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

We will where appropriate notify you by email of any changes made to our privacy policy and these changes will also be posted on this page. 

**Questions  
**  
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us  
at [ webmaster@freeweburlsubmit.com](mailto:webmaster@freeweburlsubmit.com)  
Thank you for taking the time to read our privacy policy. Our privacy policy is based on a privacy policy provided by [Privacy Policy Template](http://www.privacypolicytemplate.co.uk/) who provides a range of free website documents.
